<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AR UCSC</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
	<string name="action_help">Help</string>
	<string name="action_about">About this App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info_screen">Info Screen</string>
    <string name="button_start">Start AR</string>
    <string name="button_trip_selection">Trip Selection</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trip_selection">Trip Selection</string>
    <string name="text_nodata">No Data</string>
    <string name="title_trip_list">trips</string>
    <string name="title_trip_detail">trip Detail</string>
    <string name="text_trip_detail_heading_pinterests">Points of interest on this trip:</string>
    <string name="text_trip_detail_button_start">Start trip</string>
    <string name="text_trip_detail_button_start_relative">Demo trip</string>

    <string-array name="sorting_criteria_list">
        <item name="sorting_criterion_default">Sort by default order</item>
        <item name="sorting_criterion_alphabetical">Sort in alphabetical order</item>
        <item name="sorting_criterion_proximity">Sort by proximity</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_map">MapActivity</string>
    <string name="button_animate_route">A</string>
    <string name="button_display_route">R</string>
	<string name="help_text">The left panel shows the trips of UCSC that you can choose from.\n
	    Use the dropdown menu on the top bar to change how the trips are sorted. This can be done in 3 ways:\n
	    - by filename (default)\n
	    - alphabetically\n
	    - by proximity to the start of the trip (needs a GPS signal)\n
	    Touch a trip to see how many plcaces you will see in the right panel.\n
	    If you cannot see the complete list of locations on the trip, touch the list and scroll.\n
	    When you decide which trip you want, click the blue Start trip button!
	</string>
    <string name="help_ar_text">You are now beginning the wonderful journey in UCSC campus and follow the instructions.\n
        POINTS OF INTEREST:\n
        The name and distance of the next location are on the bottom of the screen. Use the Previous or Next buttons to skip points.\n
        When you reach the next point of interest, the app will display information about it in a box, including recent tweets.\n
        A green marker may be visible on your screen when you reach the point.\n
        Tap the marker once to view tweets, and twice to load the next POI.
	    To return to the trip selection screen, press your device\'s Back button.\n 
	    MAP:\n
        Click Show Map to display a map of the trip (needs internet). You can then display and animate the route to the next point.\n
        Blue markers are visited points, green is the next point on the trip, purple are later points on the trip.\n
        R will display the route to the next POI (if possible), and A will animate this.\n
        To return to the camera view from the map, press your device\'s Back button.
	    </string>
	<string name="help_title">Help</string>
	<string name="about_text">
	    This app was developed by Ni Di and Jia Xu\n
	    Augmented reality behaviour implemented using the\n
	    DroidAR framework (www.github.com/bitstars/droidar).\n
	    Maps behaviour implemented using Google Maps API.\n
	    Twitter feed implemented using Twitter4j.\n
	    Other sources listed in the project report.
	</string>
	<string name="about_title">About UCSC Augmented Reality</string>
</resources>
